<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss version='2.0' xmlns:atom='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom'>
<channel>
<atom:link href='http://bbss.github.io' rel='self' type='application/rss+xml'/>
<title>
I understand what I can visualize
</title>
<link>
http://bbss.github.io
</link>
<description>
Blog about code, and life in China
</description>
<lastBuildDate>
Thu, 03 Sep 2015 15:23:34 +0800
</lastBuildDate>
<generator>
clj-rss
</generator>
<item>
<guid>
http://bbss.github.io/posts/2015-09-03-blog-epoch.html
</guid>
<link>
http://bbss.github.io/posts/2015-09-03-blog-epoch.html
</link>
<title>
blog epoch
</title>
<description>
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;a name=&quot;hallo&amp;#95;wereld&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Hallo wereld&lt;/h4&gt;My name is Baruch Berger, I am a code loving guy from The Netherlands currently living in Shanghai.&lt;p&gt;It seems there are many benefits to writing about what you do so I will start to type out any interesting endevours on my beloved keyboard!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am currently trying to dig myself out of heaps of cool technologies that I want to try. Buried by the many &quot;JavaScript web framework of the season&quot;'s. And languages like JavaScript, Dart, and Python. I have recently seen the sky again and regained interest in immutable FP languages Clojure and ClojureScript. One of the biggest reasons being the focus on a short cycle of coding &lt;-&gt; seeing change, greatly increasing development speed and fun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was first introduced to Clojure in 2013 by Michiel Borkent who was a teacher of mine during my effort to gain the title of Bachelor in Software Engineering. I was by all means still very much a newbie to programming at the time having only experienced a bit of Java and C#. But Clojure left a huge impression as being the most reasonable of all options I've since come across since and many of its lessons stuck with me and carried over. Therefore I will on this blog besides showing some of my life happenings be talking a lot about all kinds of coding endeavours in those languages. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&quot;width: 100%&quot; src=&quot;img/ShanghaiPuxiToPudong.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<pubDate>
Thu, 03 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0800
</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
